<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 19:14:27 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in PSD/Finance/Trade with expertise in Adult Training and EU Policies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-psd-finance-trade-with-expertise-in-adult-training-and-eu-policies-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-psd-finance-trade-with-expertise-in-adult-training-and-eu-policies-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of the assignment is to assist DEVCO.C4 in the organisation, preparation and delivery of the training programme on Trade and Private Sector Development (TPSD) for EU staff, both at Headquarters and in Delegations in third countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, the expert will &lt;strong&gt;assist DEVCO.C4 with&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the design and delivery of the TPSD training, presenting different modules, to be agreed before each training session, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the maintenance and updating of training material, including e.g. the regular updating of the electronic training repository (containing the different presentations, technical notes, handouts and exercises), the creation of new training modules, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the logistical organisation of the training sessions in Delegations, including, among others, the preparation of course handouts (printed material, USB sticks), assisting trainees in the preparation of case studies to be presented during the training, the reservation of training rooms and equipment when abroad &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the course evaluation with a view to improving the overall quality training and &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the administrative management of hiring additional experts with specific expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in PSD/Finance/Trade with expertise in Adult Training and EU Policies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Expert will comply with the following requirements, as regards to education, skills and type of experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to one or more of the areas to be addressed during the training, or equivalent experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years&amp;#39; documented work experience in the identification, design and implementation of PSD, access to finance and Trade Related Assistance programmes in developing countries ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent facilitation skills, with a focus on hands-on practical training;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in design and delivery of adult training; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English, and a working knowledge of French and/or Spanish is a plus;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good reporting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-informed about EU trade policy and EU external aid policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversant with the principles and methodologies of project cycle management and aid delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assignment location&lt;/strong&gt;: Training in Brussels and in regional location (Mozambique indicatively envisaged at this stage, TBC)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Experts, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Team Leader will head a team of key experts, comprised of a Deputy Team Leader and four &lt;strong&gt;key experts&lt;/strong&gt; who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance including: Democracy, rule of law, human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including: Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;strong&gt;8 experts&lt;/strong&gt; (4 covering &lt;strong&gt;ACP&lt;/strong&gt; countries and 4 covering &lt;strong&gt;ENPI&lt;/strong&gt; countries). These positions are &lt;strong&gt;full time (220 man days/ year&lt;/strong&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These key experts implement the internal QC system preferably in their area of expertise and will be assigned ROM reviews/support missions according to their area of expertise, including: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PFM &amp;amp; Macroeconomics stability expertise,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They ensure timely delivery of ROM reports by ROM experts and QC checklists to EC services. They provide their inputs in their area of expertise in order to draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 12 years of experience in development cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 5 years of experience as project manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the abovementioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring, and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 3 years of experience on Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (reference no. &lt;strong&gt;ROM/KE&lt;/strong&gt;) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project not a EC COM Lot 1 Framework project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Team Leader, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-external-results-oriented-monitoring-rom</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-external-results-oriented-monitoring-rom</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Team Leader will head a team of key experts, comprised of the &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; and four other key experts who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance - Democracy, rule of law, human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including: Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;strong&gt;2 Deputy Team Leaders&lt;/strong&gt; - once covering &lt;strong&gt;ACP countries&lt;/strong&gt; and the other covering &lt;strong&gt;ENPI countries&lt;/strong&gt;.  This position is a &lt;strong&gt;full time position (220 man days/ year)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; (DTL) supports the Team Leader (TL) in fulfilling his/her tasks and responsibilities. He/she is in charge in particular of the application of the internal QC system by ROM QC experts and all ROM experts. He/she drafts the quarterly QC reports and follows-up the recommendations of the QA reports. Like the TL, he/she implements ROM reviews as a sector expert for projects and programmes and plays the role of a ROM QC expert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He/she has a minimum of 15 years of experience in development cooperation, notably in project management with a minimum of 5 years of experience as Deputy TL or TL preferably of a mixed team of long and short term experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the abovementioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring, and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 3 years and preferably 5 years of experience in quality systems in services sectors: improving work processes and efficiency, defining quality policies and objectives, implementing quality procedures. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she or the TL has a minimum of 5 years of experience on Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (&lt;strong&gt;ROM/DTL&lt;/strong&gt;) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project not a EC COM Lot 1 Framework project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will head a team of key experts, comprised of a &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; and four other &lt;strong&gt;key experts&lt;/strong&gt; who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance - Democracy; rule of law; human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including - Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;
DAI is looking for &lt;strong&gt;2 Team Leaders&lt;/strong&gt;; one to cover ACP countries and the other to cover ENPI countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;
He/she has a minimum of 15 years of experience in development cooperation with a minimum of 8 years of experience as Team Leader, preferably of a mixed team of long and short term experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the above mentioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she or the Deputy TL has a minimum of 5 years of experience on from Neighbourhood countries, preferably on Southern and/or Eastern Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (reference no.ROM/TL) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project and does not come under EC COM Lot 1.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Operations Lead</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Corporate Operations Lead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in a relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5-7 years of experience with substantial international project management and field office management experience. Management consulting experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in any of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human resources and adviser management, especially in recruitment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logistics and procurement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacity building and training;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office management, including interpreting and translation, administration, office systems, reporting; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial management, budgeting and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work independently and to handle confidential information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills and ability to prioritize and multitask.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong decision making ability and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated leadership skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive, results-oriented, creative problem solver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing, communication, analytical and negotiation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a diverse set of staff in various technical areas and at different levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted. Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/me-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/me-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;M&amp;amp;E Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor’s degree in Social Sciences (International Development), Business Administration, Economics or other related fields; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5-7 years of relevant professional experience, including 3 years in an M&amp;amp;E position with an international donor-funded development project/organization; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge and experience in application of the logical framework approach, Performance Monitoring Plan development, and environmental assessment and impact monitoring; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience of donor performance management schemes; knowledge of DFAT M&amp;amp;E processes desirable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with tracking the impacts of public-private partnerships (attribution of results, cost-sharing, etc); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in participatory design (outcome mapping, after action review, structured interviews, focus groups, case studies, surveys, and secondary data analysis techniques); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of survey design, data collection and data management, and data analysis using rigorous statistics and appropriate software; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with innovative handheld and online data collection systems; and &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with economic development programs and gender mainstreaming. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to explain M&amp;amp;E processes to staff and partners and ensure that they adhere to the highest standards of quality, relevance and timeliness in their M&amp;amp;E efforts; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills and ability to write clear reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to explain highly technical results to non-technical audiences; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with the reference &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Operations Lead</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Corporate Operations Lead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in a relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5-7 years of experience with substantial international project management and field office management experience. Management consulting experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in any of the following:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human resources and adviser management, especially in recruitment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logistics and procurement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacity building and training;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office management, including interpreting and translation, administration, office systems, reporting; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial management, budgeting and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work independently and to handle confidential information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills and ability to prioritize and multitask.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong decision making ability and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated leadership skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive, results-oriented, creative problem solver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing, communication, analytical and negotiation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a diverse set of staff in various technical areas and at different levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted. Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contractor Representative / Program Director</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contractor-representative-program-director</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contractor-representative-program-director</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contractor Representative / Program Director&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s degree required in development studies, management, or other relevant topic. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years of relevant and progressively responsible field-based experience in international development, including experience at management level. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to generate options that consider an appropriate range of capacity development supports and to translate agreed support into action. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in creating and implementing systems for logistics and procurement, contract management, human resources and adviser management, and financial and office management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to contribute to strategic thinking and planning as part of multidisciplinary teams; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness of social inclusivity and gender equality issues for implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with M4P market development approach; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience leading and managing staff in a complex cross-cultural environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to adhere to the requirements of working in an Australian Aid Program, including compliance with DFAT procedures and policies and the DFAT Code of Conduct.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills and excellent spoken and written English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent reader/speaker of Bahasa Indonesian (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Cuntries </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-cuntries</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-cuntries</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this evaluation is to assess the contribution of the EU Advisory Group in supporting the Republic of Armenia to implement its reform agenda in core areas of the EU-Armenia ENP Action Plan and the preparations for an Association Agreement, as well as the extent to which its policy advice has led to concrete policy, legal, institutional and other reforms by the Government of Armenia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Cuntries&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum Masters Degree in social sciences or 10 years professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Community programmes and EU policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and oral English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Armenian or Russian is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PC literacy, excellent writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years experience of evaluation of international donor development/cooperation and assistance in ENP, candidate or transition countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years experience in monitoring state reform processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous knowledge and experience of the ENP region is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Countries</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-countries</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-countries</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this evaluation is to assess the contribution of the EU Advisory Group in supporting the Republic of Armenia to implement its reform agenda in core areas of the EU-Armenia ENP Action Plan and the preparations for an Association Agreement, as well as the extent to which its policy advice has led to concrete policy, legal, institutional and other reforms by the Government of Armenia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Countries&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum Masters Degree in social sciences or 10 years professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU programmes and policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and oral English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Armenian or Russian is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PC literacy, excellent writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years experience of evaluation of international donor development/cooperation and assistance to ENP, candidate or transition countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years experience in monitoring state reform processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous knowledge and experience of the ENP region is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation Expert with Experience of UN Projects
</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-with-experience-of-un-projects</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-with-experience-of-un-projects</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To ensure that EC programming and contributions provide effective returns to addressing climate change in the developing world. The UNDP and Climate Parliament have managed the EU contribution. Since the EC has not managed this activity directly, this evaluation will serve as a basis for understanding lessons learned and details on the effectiveness/ appropriate use of EU funds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is to conduct an evaluation of the ED&amp;rsquo;s contribution to the PARE project. Areas such as impact, sustainability, value for money and the use of EU visibility must be examined, along with  the funding  of  workshops and workshop materials. Identification of lessons learned and recommendations for future EC contributions (support areas with maximum impact, visibility and sustainability) must also be included. An assessment of stakeholders&amp;#39; level of satisfaction with the outputs used under the EU contribution and an examination of the sustainability of implemented activities and inventions in the medium and longer term, are also requested from the consultant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work will be &lt;strong&gt;home-based&lt;/strong&gt; with 2 missions to Brussels and a field mission to one of the 10 Climate Parliament countries (Bangladesh, Congo-Brazzaville, India, Jordan, Lebanon, Morocco, Senegal, South Africa, Tanzania and Tunisia).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Evaluation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior expert, with at least 10 years of experience in evaluation  of UN projects, including experience in analysing individual donor contributions of multi-donor funded projects&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;: University degree in evaluation, project management, public administration, economics,  environmental   studies   or  technically   relevant  field,  and  Master  Degree  in evaluation,   project   management,   environment,   business  administration   or  similar  field. (Where the second  is lacking,  15 years overall  experience  in evaluation  of donor funded projects is required).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;at least 12 years of professional experience in the field of evaluation in developing countries, especially evaluating individual donor components of multi-donor projects/contributions;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;excellent writing and presentation skills, proved analytical skills and strategic thinking;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;native proficiency in English, professional competency in French&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;a good knowledge of the UN system, project finance, performance management frameworks and results-based management for development projects;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;proven experience in policy evaluations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to%20agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;agnese_ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Public Financial Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-financial-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-financial-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Public Financial Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in finance or economics, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 10 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in Public Finance Management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in public finance management agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in public financial management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in performance assessment and review of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Public Order and Security</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-order-and-security</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-order-and-security</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Public Order and Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in law or any filed related to security and law enforcement, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in security and law enforcement area;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in law enforcement agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in fighting organized crime and Intelligence-led Policing;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in performance assessment of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management-1</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in law or any filed related to border and migration management, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in border or migration management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in border or migration agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in Integrated Border Management and migration policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in performance assessment of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership skills to manage and motivate a team and to interact with project partners, the European Union Delegation to Moldova, civil society and the donor community;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in law or any filed related to border and migration management, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in border or migration management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in border or migration agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in Integrated Border Management and migration policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in performance assessment of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership skills to manage and motivate a team and to interact with project partners, the European Union Delegation to Moldova, civil society and the donor community;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
